blamefootball.com 2017-06-15

# Privacy Policy | BlameFootball

Blamefootball is committed to ensuring your privacy and keeping your personal information secure. As a result, we have drafted the following privacy policy which explains the use of information we gather.

By your use of the website, you consent to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, you should not use the service.

The policy may go through modifications if required, in which case we will update this page accordingly. We thereby advise you to check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with the changes, if any. This policy is effective from December 20, 2015.

**COLLECTED INFORMATION AND  HOW IT IS USED**

Blamefootball collects information about your visits and usage of this website, your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of the visit and number of page views.

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service.

**COOKIES**

When you visit blamefootball.com, we may send one or more cookies — a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets Blamefootball help you log in faster.

A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the website, and allow us to track your usage of blamefootball.com over time. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.

Information collected using cookies is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.

A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.

**ADVERTISING**

We currently work with third-party advertising companies, who serve ads on our website. These ads may contain cookies to collect information about your visits. This allows us to provide more relevant and interesting content to users. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by advertising network, and we do not have access to this information.

**OTHER WEBSITES**

The blamefootball.com site contains links to other websites. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, Blamefootball is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**PUBLIC FORUMS**

This site makes chat rooms, opinion polls, and news available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**SUBMITTED CONTENT**

The blamefootball.com site has a feature for users to submit their contents, which requires users to disclose their identities. Your use of such feature, and disclosure of any personal details by you through this feature, are at your sole risk.

We may store all submitted content and may also display your submitted content in any part of the service we see fit.

**GOOGLE ANALYTICS**

We are currently using Google Analytics on our site to better understand the demographics of users on our site.

**SECURITY**

We place great emphasis on the security and integrity of your information.

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

The security of your personal information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. As a result, we do not guarantee the integrity and security of the data stored in its systems, including, without limitation, your information.

**NOTIFY US**

If you have any questions, privacy concerns, complaints or comments about this Privacy Policy, please notify us by e-mail at contact@blamefootball.com
